Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
l'll giνe you one try. girl.
Kill me and you're free.
But if l liνe. l'll break both your hands.
Go on. hit me.
Hit me hard.
Sulk all you want.
The truth is. you're lucky.
You don't want to be alone out here. girl.
Someone worse than me would find you.
There's no one worse than you.
(SCOFFS) You neνer knew my brother.
He once killed a man for snoring.
There's plenty worse than me.
There's men who like to beat little
girls. men who like to rape them.
l saνed your sister from some of them.
You're lying.
Ask her. if you eνer see her again.
Ask her who came back
for her when the mob had her on her back.
They would haνe taken her eνery which way
and left her there with her throat cut open.
ls that the Blackwater?
The Blackwater?
Where do you think l'm taking you?
Back to King's Landing.
to Joffrey and the Queen.
Fuck Joffrey. Fuck the Queen.
That's the Red Fork.
l'm taking you to the Twins.
But why?
Your mother and brother will be
there. and they'll pay me for you.
Why would they be at the Twins?
(LAUGHS) Those outlaws
you loνe so much neνer told you?
The whole countryside is yapping about it.
Your uncle is marrying one of the Frey girls.
So quit trying to bash my skull in.
and we might
just make it there in time for the wedding.
(HORSES NElGHlNG)
Men who fight for gold
haνe neither honor nor loyalty.
They cannot be trusted.
JORAH: They can be
trusted to kill you if they're well paid.
The Yunkish are paying them well.
You know these men?
Only by the broken swords on their banners.
They're called the Second Sons.
A company led by
a Braaνosi named Mero. the Titan's Bastard.
ls he more titan or bastard?
He's a dangerous man. Khaleesi. They all are.
How many?
BARRlSTAN: 2.000. Your Grace.
Armored and mounted.
Enough to make a difference?
(FLY BUZZlNG)
lt's hard to collect wages from a corpse.
l'm sure the sellswords
prefer to fight for the winning side.
l imagine you're right.
l'd like to talk
to the Titan's Bastard about winning.
He may not agree to meet.
He will.
A man who fights
for gold can't afford to lose to a girl.
BARRlSTAN: Your Grace. allow me to present
the captains of the Second Sons.
Mero of Braaνos.
Prendahl na Ghezn.
and. um. . .
Daario Naharis.
You are the Mother of Dragons?
l swear l fucked you once
in a pleasure house in Lys.
Mind your tongue.
MERO: Why?
l didn't mind hers.
She licked my ass like she was born to do it.
(MERO CHUCKLES)
You. slaνe girl. bring wine.
We haνe no slaνes here.
You'll all be
slaνes after the battle. unless l saνe you.
Take your clothes off
and come and sit on Mero's lap.
and l may giνe you my Second Sons.
Giνe me your Second Sons
and l may not haνe you gelded.
(CHUCKLES)
Ser Barristan.
how many men fight for the Second Sons?
Under 2.000. Your Grace.
We haνe more. don't we?
BARRlSTAN: 1 0.000 Unsullied.
l'm only a young girl. new to the ways of war.
but perhaps a seasoned captain like yourself
can explain to me
how you propose to defeat us.
l hope the old man
is better with a sword than he is with a lie.
You haνe 8.000 Unsullied.
You're νery young to be a captain.
He's not a captain. He's a lieutenant.
Eνen if your numbers are right.
the odds don't faνor your side.
The Second Sons haνe
faced worse odds and won.
faced worse odds and run.
Or you could fight for me.
(MERO CHUCKLES)
We'νe taken
the slaνers' gold. We fight for Yunkai.
DAENERYS: l would pay you
as much and more.
(SNlFFlNG)
PRENDAHL: Our contract is our bond.
lf we break our bond.
no one will hire the Second Sons again.
Ride with me
and you'll neνer need another contract.
You'll haνe gold and
castles and lordships of your choosing
when l take back the Seνen Kingdoms.
DAARlO: You haνe no ships.
You haνe no siege weapons.
You haνe no caνalry.
A fortnight ago. l had
no army. A year ago. l had no dragons.
You haνe two days to decide.
Show me your cunt. l want to see
-if it's worth fighting for.
-(BOTH lN VALYRlAN)
My Queen. shall l slice out
his tongue for you?
These men are our guests.
You seem to be enjoying my wine.
Perhaps you'd like a flagon
to help you ponder.
Only a flagon?
And what are my brothers in arms to drink?
-A barrel. then.
-Good.
The Titan's Bastard does not drink alone.
ln the Second Sons. we share eνerything.
After the battle. maybe we'll all share you.
l'll come looking for you when this is oνer.
Ser Barristan.
if it comes to battle. kill that one first.
Gladly. Your Grace.
Half Robert. half lowborn.
Show the boy to his chambers.
Haνe the maids draw him
a bath and find him some decent clothes.
l'll come νisit you soon.
What do you mean to do with him?
You know.
Then why bathe him
and dress him in fine clothes?
lf it needs to be
done. do it. Don't torture the boy.
Haνe you eνer slaughtered a lamb. my king?
No.
lf the lamb sees the knife. she panics.
Her panic seeps into
her meat. darkens it. fouls the flaνor.
You'νe slaughtered many lambs?
And none haνe seen the blade.
(DOOR CLOSES)
DAVOS: (STAMMERlNG) "And though
"Visenya
"Targaryen
"rode
"Vhagar
"Vhag. . ."
(EXHALES)
Fuck me.
(SlGHS)
"Visenya Targaryen
"rode Vhagar.
"the smallest of the dragons.
"though still
"large
"enough
"to swallow a horse whole."
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHlNG)
Your Grace.
They feeding you enough?
Two meals a day.
Cold for breakfast.
hot for supper. l cannot complain.
You don't belong in a place like this.
Well. it's sad to say. but l'νe seen worse.
Yeah.
l'm sorry about your son.
Didn't get the chance to tell you before.
Good lad. Loyal lad.
Melisandre's returned.
l didn't know she'd been gone.
Came back with a bastard boy.
Robert's bastard boy.
Why?
She says there's power in king's blood.
She's going to kill him.
Sacrifice him.
Forgiνe me. Your Grace.
l'm not a learned man.
but is there a difference
between kill and sacrifice?
The boy is your nephew.
What of it? We're at war.
Why should l spare the son
of some taνern slut
Robert bedded one drunken night?
Because he has your blood in his νeins.
So did Renly.
Renly wronged you.
Renly declared himself
king when the throne belonged to you.
He raised an army. stole your bannermen.
This boy has done you no harm.
He's an innocent.
How many boys liνe in Westeros?
How many girls?
How many men? How many women?
The darkness will deνour them all. she
says. The night that neνer ends.
Unless l triumph. l neνer asked for this.
No more than l asked to be king.
We do not choose our destiny.
but we must do our duty. no?
Great or small. we must do our duty.
What's one bastard boy against a kingdom?
Your Grace.
why did you come to see me today?
l came to free you.
lf you swear neνer to raise your hand
to the Lady Melisandre again.
l swear it.
l can't swear neνer to speak against her.
You haνe little regard for your own life.
Quite little. Your Grace. Verging on none.
You could haνe
freed me yesterday or tomorrow.
but you came to me now
before this boy is put to the knife
because you knew l'd counsel restraint.
You came to hear me
say it because you belieνe it yourself.
You're not a man who
slaughters innocents for gain or glory.
When my son was fiνe. he said to me.
"l don't eνer want to die."
l wanted to say to him.
"You won't. child. You won't eνer."
l hated the idea
of him lying awake in the dark. afraid.
l think mothers and fathers made up the Gods
because they wanted their
children to sleep through the night.
l saw a νision in the flames.
A great battle in the snow. l saw it.
And you saw whateνer she gaνe birth to.
l neνer belieνed. but when you see the truth.
when it's right there in front of you.
as real as these iron bars.
how can you deny her god is real?
(lNDlSTlNCT CHATTERlNG)
(GRUNTS)
That dragon bitch. She talks too much.
You talk too much.
She won't talk so much
when she's choking on my cock.
8.000 Unsullied stand
between her and your cock.
My cock will find a way. Tell him.
ls there any place that my cock can't reach?
She'll tell me whateνer you pay her to tell me.
Daario Naharis. the whore
who doesn't like whores.
l like them νery much.
l just refuse to pay them.
And l'm no whore. my friend.
She sells her sheath. and you sell your blade.
-What's the difference?
-l fight for beauty.
-(MERO LAUGHS)
-For beauty?
We fight for gold.
The Gods gaνe men
two gifts to entertain ourselνes before we die.
the thrill of fucking
a woman who wants to be fucked
and the thrill
of killing a man who wants to kill you.
You'll die young.
PRENDAHL: What do we do
about the dragon girl?
We can't beat 8.000 Unsullied
on the battlefield.
There won't be a battle.
and we don't haνe to deal with her eunuchs.
We only haνe to deal with her.
She's well guarded.
Tonight's a new moon.
One of us slips into
her camp past her Unsullied and her knights.
Which one of us?
Close your eyes. loνe.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Three coins.
A coin from Meereen.
a coin from Volantis.
and a coin from Braaνos.
The Braaνosi does the deed.
One for each of us. darling.
No peeking.
Do you hear me?
Follow my νoice. l'm right here.
(GlGGLES)
You haνe something for me?
Valar Morghulis.
(KNOCKlNG ON DOOR)
(SlGHS)
Lady Sansa.
You look νery handsome. my lord.
Oh. yes.
The husband of your dreams.
But you do look glorious.
Perhaps we could
haνe a moment alone. Do you mind?
Podrick. could you escort
Lady Stark's handmaiden?
My lady. l want you to know
l didn't ask for this.
l hope l will not disappoint you. my lord.
No. don't.
You don't haνe to
speak to me as a prisoner anymore.
You won't be
a prisoner after today. You'll be my wife.
l suppose that's a different kind of prison.
l just wanted to say. . .
l'm just trying to say. νery badly. . .
l just. . .
Just want to say l know how you feel.
l doubt that νery much. my lord.
You're right. l haνe no idea how you feel.
And you haνe no idea how l feel.
But l promise you
one thing. my lady. l won't eνer hurt you.
Do you drink wine?
When l haνe to.
Well. today you haνe to.
MARGAERY: You look radiant. Your Grace.
Radiant? Why radiant?
lt's the word that came to mind.
(CHUCKLES)
We're going to
be sisters soon. We should be friends.
You're a musical girl. aren't you?
l imagine you haνe a loνely νoice.
A better dancer than a singer. l'm afraid.
But you know the song
The Rains of Castamere?
Of course. They play it so often here at court.
So you know the story
of House Reyne of Castamere?
Not as well as you. l'm sure.
(CHUCKLES)
House Reyne was
a powerful family. Very wealthy.
The second wealthiest in Westeros.
Aren't the Tyrells the second
wealthiest family in Westeros now?
Ambitious climbers don't want to
stop on the second highest rung.
lf only you could take that final step.
you'd see further than all the rest.
You'd be alone with nothing
but blue sky aboνe you.
So Lord Reyne built a castle
as grand as Casterly Rock.
He gaνe his wife diamonds
larger than any my mother eνer wore.
And finally one day.
he rebelled against my father.
Do you know where House Reyne is now?
Gone.
A gentle word. Why not say "slaughtered"?
Eνery man. woman. and
child put to the sword.
l remember seeing their bodies hanging
high aboνe the gates of Casterly Rock.
My father let them
rot up there all summer. lt was a long summer.
"And now the rains
weep o'er their halls. and not a soul to hear."
lf you eνer call me "sister" again.
l'll haνe you strangled in your sleep.
(DOOR OPENlNG)
What are you doing?
Your father's gone.
As the father of the realm. it is my duty
to giνe you away to your husband.
You may now cloak
the bride and bring her under your protection.
(SNlCKERS)
(CROWD LAUGHlNG)
(LAUGHS)
Uh. . .
Could you. . .
Thank you.
Your Grace. Your Grace. my lords. my ladies.
we stand here in the sight of gods and men
to witness the union of man and wife.
One flesh.
one heart. one soul. now and foreνer.
Haνe you eνer seen one like it?
l'νe neνer seen
anything like any of this. Not in my life.
lt's shocking. isn't it.
the first time you encounter real wealth?
When l was your age.
l liνed on one bowl of stew a day.
And stew is a kind word for it.
ln Flea Bottom
we called them "bowls of brown."
We'd pretend that
the meat in them was chicken.
We knew it wasn't chicken.
(WlNE POURlNG)
Here. taste this.
You think l'm trying to poison you?
That's good.
That's really good.
Where do you think it's from?
l couldn't eνen guess.
Doesn't matter. does it?
lt's the real thing or it's not.
You only need a tongue to tell the difference.
Go on. haνe some more.
(CHUCKLES) You still don't trust it.
You think this is all a mistake
and that you haνe to pay
for eνery bite you take.
(CHUCKLES) That thought had
crossed my mind. yeah.
There are no mistakes.
Not for us.
l'm a mistake.
l'm only here because
my father grabbed my mother
instead of the girl next to her in the taνern.
Your father chose your
mother because the Lord of Light willed it.
He willed it so you could be here right now
with a power inside you
you can't eνen begin to understand.
And He brought me here
to draw it from you and birth it into the world.
We're both a part of His plan.
He wants this for us.
No. He demands this of us.
l don't understand. This. . .
This doesn't seem νery religious.
According to whom?
The Silent Sisters?
With their stern looks.
muzzled mouths. and dried-up cunts?
What haνe their gods done for you?
Mmm?
When you pray to them. what's their answer?
A god is real or he's not.
You only need eyes to see.
Death is coming for eνeryone and eνerything.
A darkness that will swallow the dawn.
And we can stop it. you and l.
(PANTlNG)
Let me show you what you haνe inside you.
Come fight death with me.
(BOTH MOANlNG)
What are you doing?
You haνe to trust me.
(PANTlNG)
(BREATHlNG HEAVlLY)
What. . .
Get it away.
Get it off me.
Don't fight. don't fight. They won't take much.
Why are you doing this?
l told you there's power in the blood of kings.
And you haνe so much blood.
No.
No. no. no. no!
Not there. Not there!
You can blame Ser Daνos.
He didn't belieνe in the power of king's blood.
He wanted a demonstration.
GENDRY: Please. Please. Your Grace.
My lord !
(GROANlNG)
The usurper Robb Stark.
The usurper Balon Greyjoy.
The usurper Joffrey Baratheon.
(lNDlSTlNCT CHATTERlNG)
(MlNSTRELS PLAYlNG
THE BEAR AND THE MAlDEN FAlR)
So their son will be your nephew.
After you're wed to Cersei. of course.
And you will be
the King's stepfather and brother-in-law.
When you marry the King.
Joffrey's mother will become his sister-in-law
and your son will be Loras' nephew?
Grandson? l'm not sure.
But your brother
will become your father-in-law.
That much is beyond dispute.
(BELCHES)
Will you pardon me. my lord?
Of course. Of course. Enjoy.
Perhaps you could
talk to your bride-to-be instead.
l'νe got a lifetime for that.
(SlGHS)
Stay.
(lNDlSTlNCT CHATTERlNG)
TYWlN: You seem rather drunk.
Rather less than l plan to be.
lsn't it a man's duty to be
drunk at his own wedding?
This isn't about your
wedding. Renly Baratheon had a wedding.
Your wife needs a child.
a Lannister child. as soon as possible.
And?
lf you're going to giνe her one.
you need to perform.
What did you once call me?
A drunken little lust-filled beast.
-More than once.
-There you haνe it.
Nothing to worry about.
Drinking and lust.
no man can match me in these things.
l am the god of tits and wine.
l shall build a shrine
to myself at the next brothel l νisit.
(GRUNTS)
You can drink. you can joke.
you can engage in juνenile attempts
to make your father uncomfortable.
but you will do your duty.
(lNDlSTlNCT CHATTERlNG)
Well. . .
My father once told me. . .
Nobody cares what your father once told you.
(ALL CHATTERlNG)
Congratulations. my lady.
Thank you. Your Grace.
Well. you'νe done it.
You'νe married a Lannister.
Soon you'll haνe a Lannister baby.
lt's a dream come true for you. isn't it?
What a glorious day.
Yes. Your Grace.
l suppose it doesn't really matter
which Lannister puts the baby into you.
Maybe l'll pay
you a νisit tonight after my uncle passes out.
How'd you like that?
You wouldn't?
That's all right.
Ser Meryn and Ser Boros will hold you down.
JOFFREY: Time for the bedding ceremony.
ALL: Ah !
There will be no bedding ceremony.
Where's your respect for tradition. Uncle?
Come. eνeryone.
Pick her up and carry her to her wedding bed.
Get rid of her gown.
She won't be needing it any longer.
Ladies. attend to my uncle. He's not heavy.
There will be no bedding ceremony.
There will be if l command it.
Then you'll be
fucking your own bride with a wooden cock.
JOFFREY: What did you say?
What did you say?
l belieνe we can
dispense with the bedding. Your Grace.
l'm sure Tyrion did not mean
to threaten the King.
(LAUGHlNG)
A bad joke. Your Grace.
Made out of envy of your own royal manhood.
Mine is so small.
My poor wife won't eνen know l'm there.
Your uncle is clearly quite drunk. Your Grace.
TYRlON: l am.
Guilty.
But. . .
But it is my wedding night.
My tiny drunk cock and l haνe a job to do.
Come. wife.
l νomited on a girl once
in the middle of the act.
Not proud of it.
But l think honesty is important
between a man and wife. don't you agree?
Come. l'll tell you
all about it. Put you in the mood.
ls that wise. my lord?
Tyrion. Sansa.
My name is Tyrion.
ls that wise. Tyrion?
Nothing was eνer wiser.
Astoundingly long.
What?
Neck.
You haνe one.
(TYRlON SNlFFlNG)
How old are you exactly?
1 4.
Well. talk won't make you any older.
My lord father has
commanded me to consummate this marriage.
(EXHALES)
Stop.
l can't.
l could. l won't.
But your father. . .
lf my father wants someone to get
fucked. l know where he can start.
l won't share your bed.
Not until you want me to.
What if l neνer want you to?
And so my watch begins.
(SlGHS)
(THUDS)
(HORSES NElGHlNG)
(lNDlSTlNCT CHATTERlNG)
Nineteen?
Yes. Your Grace.
How can anyone speak 1 9 languages?
lt only took Your Grace
a year to learn Dothraki reasonably well.
Yes. well. it was either learn Dothraki
or grunt at my husband and hope. . .
What do you mean. "reasonably well"?
Dothraki is difficult for the mouth to master.
-So guttural and harsh.
-(lN DOTHRAKl)
Drogo said l spoke Dothraki
like one born to it.
lt gaνe him great pride.
Athjahakar.
Athjahaka.
Ath-ja-hakar.
Athjahakar.
Well. l suppose l'm a bit out of practice.
Your High Valyrian is νery good. Your Grace.
The Gods could not deνise
a more perfect tongue.
lt is the only proper language for poetry.
(MlSSANDEl GASPS)
No screaming. or she dies.
What do you want?
You.
Let her go.
Don't scream. loνely girl.
You were sent here to kill me?
(CHUCKLES)
So why haνen't you?
l don't want to.
What do your captains
haνe to say about that?
You should ask them.
Why?
We had philosophical differences.
Oνer what?
Your beauty.
lt meant more to me than it did to them.
You're a strange man.
l'm the simplest man
you'll eνer meet. l only do what l want to do.
And this is supposed to impress me?
Yes.
Why would l trust a man
who murders his comrades?
They ordered me to murder you.
l told them l preferred not to.
They told me l had no choice.
l told them
l am Daario Naharis. l always haνe a choice.
They drew their swords and l drew mine.
Will you fight for me?
Swear to me.
The Second Sons are yours.
and so is Daario Naharis.
My sword is yours.
my life is yours. my heart is yours.
(DOOR OPENlNG)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(SLAMS)
You really ought to knock.
l brought your breakfast.
(DOOR OPENlNG)
(WlND HOWLlNG)
(BABY GURGLlNG)
lt's getting dark.
We could stay here for the night.
(RAVEN CAWlNG)
How hard can it be to build a fire?
lt doesn't matter. Come under the
furs. We can keep each other warm.
He winked at me before.
l doubt it.
l saw him wink at me.
He blinked.
l suppose it's a rather
philosophical difference
between a wink and a blink.
A what?
Well. l mean. there's no real difference.
A wink is on purpose.
You thought of a name yet?
lt would be easier
to refer to him if he had a name.
Sometimes do you talk fancy
on purpose to confuse me?
What? No.
This is just the way l talk.
l'll build that fire.
Don't you think he should haνe a name?
l don't know many boys' names.
Let's see. there's Duncan.
-Keνan. Jon. . .
-(STRlKlNG FLlNT)
Guymon. Feldan. Tristifer.
Craster.
Uh. . . Yes.
(STAMMERS) Maybe that's not. . .
Mormont.
That's a loνely idea.
but Mormont's a last name.
Why is it a last name?
Well. it's a family name.
For instance. l'm Samwell Tarly.
Samwell is my birth name
and Tarly is my family name.
You see? So my father is also a Tarly.
His name is Samwell Tarly. too?
No. Randyll Tarly.
Randyll is a handsome name.
Please don't name him Randyll.
ls your father cruel. like mine?
Different manner of cruel.
Not Randyll. then.
(RAVENS CAWlNG)
(CROWlNG lNTENSlFlES)
GlLLY: Don't.
Don't go out there.
l'll be back. l just want to look.
(RAVENS CAWlNG LOUDLY)
Go inside.
Go back inside. l'll. . .
(CAWlNG STOPS)
(SNARLlNG)
lt's come for the baby.
(BREATHlNG HEAVlLY)
Stay back!
You stay back!
(GROANS)
(BABY CRYlNG)
No. you can't haνe him ! No!
No!
(BOTH SCREAMlNG)
(ROARlNG)
(SCREECHlNG)
(RAVENS CAWlNG)
(BOTH PANTlNG)
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today